{"sid": "TGEZJMUNR4LY_main", "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 3, "start_time": 722567, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 722571, "question": "7+3+4", "correct_answer": 14, "events": [["submit", 727643]], "time_left_end": "295", "answered_time": 727643, "user_answer": "14", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "295", "question_time_start": 727644, "question": "8+3+7+4", "correct_answer": 22, "events": [["submit", 733913]], "time_left_end": "289", "answered_time": 733913, "user_answer": "22", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "289", "question_time_start": 733914, "question": "3+6+7", "correct_answer": 16, "events": [["submit", 736830]], "time_left_end": "286", "answered_time": 736830, "user_answer": "16", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "286", "question_time_start": 736831, "question": "4+3+8+6", "correct_answer": 21, "events": [["submit", 746032]], "time_left_end": "277", "answered_time": 746032, "user_answer": "21", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "277", "question_time_start": 746033, "question": "7+68", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["submit", 751250]], "time_left_end": "272", "answered_time": 751250, "user_answer": "75", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "272", "question_time_start": 751251, "question": "9+3", "correct_answer": 12, "events": [["submit", 753740]], "time_left_end": "269", "answered_time": 753740, "user_answer": "12", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "269", "question_time_start": 753741, "question": "3+97", "correct_answer": 100, "events": [["submit", 756153]], "time_left_end": "267", "answered_time": 756153, "user_answer": "100", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "267", "question_time_start": 756154, "question": "4+4+17", "correct_answer": 25, "events": [["submit", 762358]], "time_left_end": "261", "answered_time": 762358, "user_answer": "25", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "261", "question_time_start": 762358, "question": "7+43", "correct_answer": 50, "events": [["submit", 765546]], "time_left_end": "258", "answered_time": 765546, "user_answer": "50", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "258", "question_time_start": 765549, "question": "6+4", "correct_answer": 10, "events": [["submit", 767061]], "time_left_end": "256", "answered_time": 767061, "user_answer": "10", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 4, "start_time": 767062, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "256", "question_time_start": 767062, "question": "8+8+19", "correct_answer": 35, "events": [["submit", 772378]], "time_left_end": "251", "answered_time": 772378, "user_answer": "35", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "251", "question_time_start": 772379, "question": "6+4+76", "correct_answer": 86, "events": [["submit", 775750]], "time_left_end": "247", "answered_time": 775750, "user_answer": "86", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "247", "question_time_start": 775751, "question": "44+96", "correct_answer": 140, "events": [["submit", 781085]], "time_left_end": "242", "answered_time": 781085, "user_answer": "140", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "242", "question_time_start": 781086, "question": "6+7+6+8", "correct_answer": 27, "events": [["submit", 786987]], "time_left_end": "236", "answered_time": 786987, "user_answer": "27", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "236", "question_time_start": 786988, "question": "9+4+7+4", "correct_answer": 24, "events": [["submit", 792656]], "time_left_end": "230", "answered_time": 792655, "user_answer": "24", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "230", "question_time_start": 792658, "question": "3+3+4+4", "correct_answer": 14, "events": [["submit", 796589]], "time_left_end": "226", "answered_time": 796589, "user_answer": "14", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "226", "question_time_start": 796590, "question": "3+64", "correct_answer": 67, "events": [["submit", 799843]], "time_left_end": "223", "answered_time": 799843, "user_answer": "67", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "223", "question_time_start": 799844, "question": "7+43", "correct_answer": 50, "events": [["submit", 802597]], "time_left_end": "220", "answered_time": 802597, "user_answer": "50", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "220", "question_time_start": 802598, "question": "4+8+8", "correct_answer": 20, "events": [["submit", 805982]], "time_left_end": "217", "answered_time": 805982, "user_answer": "20", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "217", "question_time_start": 805986, "question": "4+8+3", "correct_answer": 15, "events": [["submit", 808596]], "time_left_end": "214", "answered_time": 808596, "user_answer": "19", "user_correct": "False", "score": "18"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 5, "start_time": 808597, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "214", "question_time_start": 808597, "question": "26+57", "correct_answer": 83, "events": [["submit", 820823]], "time_left_end": "202", "answered_time": 820823, "user_answer": "83", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "202", "question_time_start": 820824, "question": "8+9+33", "correct_answer": 50, "events": [["submit", 829710]], "time_left_end": "193", "answered_time": 829710, "user_answer": "50", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "193", "question_time_start": 829711, "question": "43+23", "correct_answer": 66, "events": [["submit", 834980]], "time_left_end": "188", "answered_time": 834980, "user_answer": "66", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "188", "question_time_start": 834981, "question": "8+6+33", "correct_answer": 47, "events": [["submit", 841564]], "time_left_end": "181", "answered_time": 841564, "user_answer": "47", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "181", "question_time_start": 841565, "question": "4+8+8+4", "correct_answer": 24, "events": [["submit", 846164]], "time_left_end": "177", "answered_time": 846164, "user_answer": "24", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "177", "question_time_start": 846166, "question": "3+7+9+34", "correct_answer": 53, "events": [["submit", 855608]], "time_left_end": "167", "answered_time": 855608, "user_answer": "53", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "167", "question_time_start": 855609, "question": "4+4+87", "correct_answer": 95, "events": [["submit", 862656]], "time_left_end": "160", "answered_time": 862656, "user_answer": "85", "user_correct": "False", "score": "23"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "160", "question_time_start": 862657, "question": "3+4+4+8", "correct_answer": 19, "events": [["submit", 870977]], "time_left_end": "152", "answered_time": 870977, "user_answer": "19", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "152", "question_time_start": 870978, "question": "6+69", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["submit", 876013]], "time_left_end": "147", "answered_time": 876013, "user_answer": "75", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "147", "question_time_start": 876017, "question": "4+58", "correct_answer": 62, "events": [["submit", 881253]], "time_left_end": "142", "answered_time": 881253, "user_answer": "62", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 6, "start_time": 881254, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "142", "question_time_start": 881254, "question": "4+7+37", "correct_answer": 48, "events": [["submit", 886901]], "time_left_end": "136", "answered_time": 886901, "user_answer": "48", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "136", "question_time_start": 886902, "question": "6+9+3+28", "correct_answer": 46, "events": [["submit", 897040]], "time_left_end": "126", "answered_time": 897040, "user_answer": "46", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "126", "question_time_start": 897041, "question": "53+86", "correct_answer": 139, "events": [["submit", 902197]], "time_left_end": "121", "answered_time": 902197, "user_answer": "139", "user_correct": "True", "score": "29"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "121", "question_time_start": 902198, "question": "4+88+53", "correct_answer": 145, "events": [["open_calc", 913370], ["calc_5", 914887], ["calc_3", 915271], ["calc_+", 915634], ["calc_8", 916105], ["calc_8", 916251], ["calc_+", 916753], ["calc_4", 917320], ["calc_=", 917856], ["submit", 922921]], "calculator_opened": "True", "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "100", "answered_time": 922921, "user_answer": "145", "user_correct": "True", "score": "30"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "100", "question_time_start": 922922, "question": "8+4+7+53", "correct_answer": 72, "events": [["open_calc", 925022], ["calc_5", 926274], ["calc_3", 926639], ["calc_+", 927009], ["calc_7", 927692], ["calc_+", 928476], ["calc_4", 929108], ["calc_+", 929725], ["calc_8", 930276], ["calc_=", 931008], ["submit", 936266]], "calculator_opened": "True", "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "87", "answered_time": 936266, "user_answer": "72", "user_correct": "True", "score": "31"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "87", "question_time_start": 936267, "question": "53+58", "correct_answer": 111, "events": [["submit", 943681]], "time_left_end": "79", "answered_time": 943681, "user_answer": "111", "user_correct": "True", "score": "32"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "79", "question_time_start": 943682, "question": "78+43", "correct_answer": 121, "events": [["submit", 952718]], "time_left_end": "70", "answered_time": 952718, "user_answer": "121", "user_correct": "True", "score": "33"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "70", "question_time_start": 952720, "question": "4+3+98", "correct_answer": 105, "events": [["submit", 960621]], "time_left_end": "62", "answered_time": 960621, "user_answer": "105", "user_correct": "True", "score": "34"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "62", "question_time_start": 960623, "question": "8+6+8+4", "correct_answer": 26, "events": [["submit", 965811]], "time_left_end": "57", "answered_time": 965811, "user_answer": "26", "user_correct": "True", "score": "35"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "57", "question_time_start": 965813, "question": "3+9+9+8", "correct_answer": 29, "events": [["submit", 973065]], "time_left_end": "50", "answered_time": 973065, "user_answer": "29", "user_correct": "True", "score": "36"}}}, "block_4": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 973065, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "50", "question_time_start": 973065, "question": "4+8+6+78", "correct_answer": 96, "events": [["submit", 981648]], "time_left_end": "41", "answered_time": 981648, "user_answer": "96", "user_correct": "True", "score": "37"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "41", "question_time_start": 981649, "question": "94+733", "correct_answer": 827, "events": [["submit", 999128]], "time_left_end": "24", "answered_time": 999128, "user_answer": "827", "user_correct": "True", "score": "38"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "24", "question_time_start": 999129, "question": "8+7+9+46", "correct_answer": 70, "events": [["submit", 1016416]], "time_left_end": "7", "answered_time": 1016416, "user_answer": "70", "user_correct": "True", "score": "39"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "7", "question_time_start": 1016418, "question": "4+87+38", "correct_answer": 129, "events": [["open_calc", 1018555], ["calc_3", 1020453], ["calc_8", 1020918], ["calc_+", 1021423], ["calc_8", 1022121]], "calculator_opened": "True"}}}}}